So let's recap.
那么我们来复习一下
We have our data which is all these students.
我们得到所有这些学生的数据
The blue ones have been accepted and the red ones have been rejected.
蓝点代表接受的学生 红点代表拒绝的学生
And we have our model which consists of the equation two times test plus grades minus 18,
我们得到的模型包含方程式 2*Test+Grades-18
which gives rise to this boundary which
可以得到这个边界线
the point where the score is zero and a prediction.
其中分数为 0 和一个预测
The prediction says that the student gets accepted of the score is positive or zero,
预测说明如果分数大于等于 0 则学生被接受
and rejected if the score is negative.
如果分数为负 学生被拒绝
So now we'll introduce the notion of a preceptron,
所以现在我们介绍感知器的概念
which is the building block of neural networks,
这是神经网络的基础
and it's just an encoding of our equation into a small graph.
是指把我们的方程式进行编码 形成小图形
The way we've build it is the following.
我们构建的方式如下
Here we have our data and our boundary line and we fit it inside a node.
这是我们的数据和分界线 我们在节点内进行拟合
And now we add small nodes for the inputs which,
现在我们增加输入的小节点
in this case, they are the test and the grades.
在这个例子中分别是测试 (Test) 和分数 (Grades)
Here we can see an example where test equals seven and grades equals six.
在这个例子中我们可以看到 测试为 7 分数为 6
And what the perceptron does is it blocks the points seven,
感知器要做的是把点 (7,6) 绘制在图中
six and checks if the point is in the positive or negative area.
并检查这个点位于正区域还是负区域
If the point is in the positive area,
如果这个点位于正区域
then it returns a yes.
会返回 是
And if it is in the negative area, it returns and no.
如果位于负区域 会返回 否
So let's recall that our equation is score equals two
我们来回忆下方程式
times test plus one times grade minus 18,
Score = 2*Test+Grades-18
and that our prediction consists of accepting
我们预测包括 如果分数为正数或 0
the student if the score is positive or zero,
那么接受这个学生
and rejecting them if the score is negative.
如果分数为负 就会拒绝这个学生
These weights two, one, and minus 18,
这些权重 2、1 和 -18
are what define the linear equation,
定义了线性方程式
and so we'll use them as labels in the graph.
所以我们在图形中使用它们作为标签
The two and the one will label the edges coming from X1 and X 2 respectively,
2 和 1 分别标记了 X1 和 X2 的边
and the bias unit minus 18 will label the node.
而偏置单元 -18 标记了节点
Thus, when we see a node with these labels,
我们看到含有这些标签的节点
we can think of the linear equation they generate.
想起它们生成的线性方程式
Another way to grab this node is to consider the bias as part of the input.
另一种抓取这个节点的方式是把偏差考虑成输入的一部分
Now since W1 gets multiplied by X1 and W2 by X2,
既然 W1 乘以 X1  W2 乘以 X2
It's natural to think that B gets multiplied by a one.
很容易可以想到 B 乘以 1
So we'll have the B labeling and and edge coming from a one.
所以我们可以标记 B 边缘为 1
Then what the node does is it multiplies the values coming from
那么这个节点可以把输入节点的值
the incoming nodes by the values and the corresponding edges.
乘以对应边缘的值
Then it adds them and finally,
然后添加它们
it checks if the result is greater that are equal to zero.
最后检查结果是否大于等于 0
If it is, then the node returns a yes or a value of one,
如果是 那么节点返回 是 以及值 1
and if it isn't then the node returns a no or a value of zero.
如果不是 那么节点返回 否 以及值 0
We'll be using both notations throughout
我们会在课程中同时使用两种符号记法
this class although the second one will be used more often.
虽然第二个更为常用
In the general case,
在通常情况下
this is how the nodes look.
这是节点是这样的
We will have our node over here then end inputs coming
我们在这里有节点 然后添加输入
in with values X1 up to Xn and one,
值 X1 到 Xn 和 1
and edges with weights W1 up to Wn,
边缘为权重 W1 到 Wn
and B corresponding to the bias unit.
B 对应偏置单元
And then the node calculates the linear equation Wx plus B,
那么节点计算线性方程 Wx+B
which is a summation from I equals one to n,
即对 Wixi+B 求和
of WIXI plus B.
其中 i 为 1 到 n
This node then checks if the value is zero or bigger, and if it is,
然后节点检查了值是否大于等于0
then the node returns a value of one for yes and if not,
如果是 那么返回值 1 和是
then it returns a value of zero for no.
如果不是 那么返回值 0 和否
Note that we're using an implicit function,
注意我们使用一个隐函数
here, which is called a step function.
又称为阶跃函数
What the step function does is it returns a one if the input is positive or zero,
如果输入为正数或 0 阶跃函数返回 1
and a zero if the input is negative.
如果输入为负 阶跃函数返回 0
So in reality, these perceptrons can be seen as a combination of nodes,
那么实际上 这些感知器可以看作节点的组合
where the first node calculates a linear equation and the inputs on the weights,
其中第一个节点计算线性方程式和权重上的输入
and the second node applies the step function to the result.
第二个节点把阶跃函数应用到结果中
These can be graphed as follows:
可以用以下图形进行表示
the summation sign represents a linear function in the first node,
求和符号代表第一个节点的线性函数
and the drawing represents a step function in the second node.
绘图表示第二个节点的阶跃函数
In the future, we will use different step functions.
随后我们会使用不同的阶跃函数
So this is why it's useful to specify it in the node.
因此这是说明节点中指明阶跃函数有效性的原因
So as we've seen there are two ways to represent perceptions.
正如我们所了解的 感知器有两种表示方法
The one on the left has a bias unit coming from an input node with a value of one,
左侧是把偏置单元作为一个输入节点
and the one in the right has the bias inside the node.
右侧则是在节点中包含了误差